[{"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有1层，下面有3层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 5], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有5层，下面有3层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 9], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有4层，下面有1层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 6], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有1层，下面有2层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3, 4], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有2层，下面有1层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 4], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有5层，下面有1层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 7], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有5层，下面有2层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3, 8], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有1层，下面有7层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [8, 9], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有6层，下面有2层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [3, 9], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有1层，下面有1层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 3], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有1层，下面有5层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6, 7], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有1层，下面有4层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5, 6], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有2层，下面有5层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6, 8], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有2层，下面有6层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [7, 9], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有2层，下面有4层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5, 7], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}, {"body": [{"title": "看图填一填", "stem": "看图填一填", "houseImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/单楼层.svg", "personImg": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg", "bubbleImg": "v2/组件/认识上下/气泡2.svg", "textList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "我家上面有7层，下面有1层。"}]], "inputList": [[{"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/人物/人物头像系列/女孩/19.svg"}, {"type": "text", "value": "家在"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "这栋楼一共有"}, {"type": "num", "value": ""}, {"type": "text", "value": "层"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-input9", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 9], "knowledges": ["认识上下"], "resource": "resource", "type": "填空", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-2-11"}]